Just gonna stand there and watch me burn
That's all right cause I like the way it hurts
Just gonna stand there and hear me burn
That's all right cause I like the way it lies
I love the way it lies
I can't tell you what it really is
I can tell you what it feels like
And right now this is still a nightmare of me
I can't breathe but I still fight
While I can't fight as long as the wall feels right
It's like I'm in it's like high above
Troph on my head
It's like I'm often hanging and I love it
The more I suffer
I stop the chain and break the form
I'm about to drown
She just not to taste me
She fucking hates me
And I love it way
Where you going?
I'm leaving you
Come back
We're running right back
Here we go again
So insane cause when it's going
It's going great
I'm super married
But the wind is back
She's not a slave
But when it's bad it's awful
I feel slow to say
Who's that to?
I don't even know his name
I laid hands on her
I never stood so long again
I guess I don't know my old dreams
Just gonna stand there
And watch me burn
That's all right cause I like the way it hurts
Just gonna stand there and hear me burn
That's all right cause I love the way it hurts
Love the way it hurts
Give her a love song
You can barely breathe
When you're breathing and you meet
And neither one of you
Even though it hit her
Got the wrong fuzzy feeling
Get it, she'll use the kid on her
You can't fucking stick her up to let him
You're slow, you never hit her
And I never do nothing
I've heard her lay her in each other's face
When you hit her in any births
When you spit him
You boost point
So the sad scratch pops
And on top
And I was a loss in my moments
When you hit her
And you're surprised that it's a car break
And chose to go
So I say I passed the car
You said it backwards
Guess it's bad on her
Cause today
That was just the day
Yes, the day is always a different day
So I like broken back
It's bad over for your problem
It's not
Next time it's over
You don't kiddin' of a kid
It's like there's no agenda game
But you like it
Now you get to watch a read
About the window
Guess what I call it
Windowplay
Just gonna stand there
Watch me burn
But I saw it
Cause I like broken back
Just gonna stand there
And hear me burn
I saw it
Cause I love the way
Like
I love the way you lie
Now I know we said things
Big things
That we didn't mean
And we saw it back
And it's the same pattern
Same thing
But you're simply too bad as mine
You're saying it's me
When it comes to love you
Just as blinded
Baby please come back
It wasn't you
Baby you was me
Maybe our relationship
Is in this crazy
Is this things
Maybe this is what happens
When a torn name
meets a volcano
When I know it's not
Love you too much
Talk right up
Come inside
Pick up your bags
On the sidewalk
Don't do it
It's a fairy
My voice when I talk
Talk to this is my fault
Look me in the alcohol
Next time I press the name
Of this
At the trial wall
Next time
There will be no next time
I apologize
Even though I know it's nice
I'm tired of the games
I just want to best
I know I'm alive
She ever tries to fucking leave a kid
I'm attached to the pen
And said the song so far
She's gone
I'm there
Watch me
But
When I saw it
It was like
Waiter
Just go
And stop there
And hear me
But
When I saw it
It was like
I was waiting
I love you.