Just gonna stand there and watch me burn
That's alright cause I like the way it hurts
Just gonna stand there and hear me burn
That's alright cause I like the way it lies
I love the way it lies
I can't tell you what it really is
I can tell you what it feels like
And right now this is still a nightmare of me
I can't breathe, but I still fight
While I can't fight
As long as the wall feels right
It's like I'm in it's like
I have a lot of trouble I hate
It's like I'm often hanging in a love of the wall
I stop the chain and break the form
I'm about to drown
She just not to taste me
She fucking hates me
And I love it, wait
Where you going?
I'm leaving you
Oh yeah, come back
We're running right back
Here we go again
So insane
Cause when it's going good
It's gonna be great
I'm super married
But the wind is bad
She's not a slave from when it's bad
It's awful
I feel slow to say
Who's that to?
I don't even know his name
I laid hands on her
I never stood so long again
I guess I don't know my own strength
Just gonna stand there and watch me burn
That's alright cause I like the way it hurts
Just gonna stand there and hear me burn
That's alright cause I love the way it hurts
I love the way it hurts
If I love somebody so much
You barely breathe when you're breathing
And neither one of you
Even though it hit him
Got the wrong fuzzy feeling
Get him chills
You stick hit him
And are you beating so hard
You stick hooked in at him
You school you never hit him
Never didn't learn
There were no other nations
In each other's space
It wouldn't be in him any burst
When he spit him
You pushed point to the sand
Scrat's coffin on top
And I was lost in my moments
And I used the phrase
Did it count?
Raking, choses, both
So I say I best echo
You sit between ways
Get me fat on your chest today
That was just the joke
Yes, I'm dead
It's all worth a different day
You select yourself
And I quit playing over
But you problemless stuff
Next time is so great
You don't kiddin' another chance
Life is no pretend a game
But you like it
Now you get to want to read about the window, guess it's what I call it, window play.
Just gonna stand there, watch me burn.
But I saw it because I like the way it hurts.
Just gonna stand there and hear me burn.
That's all right because I love the way it lies.
I love the way it lies.
Now I know we said things, things, things that we didn't mean.
And we fall back into the same pattern.
Same team, but you're simply too bad as mine.
You're saying it's me when it comes to love.
You just invited me.
Please come back.
It wasn't you.
Baby, you was me.
Maybe our relationship isn't as crazy as it seems.
Maybe that's what happens when a torn name meets a volcano.
I know it's gonna love you so much.
Talk right up, come inside.
Pick up your bags on the side, Bob.
Don't you hear me?
My voice will not talk to you.
This is my Bob.
Look me in the eye, Bob.
Next time I press the name of this perpetrator, Bob.
Next time there will be no next time.
I apologize even though I know it's nice.
I'm tired of the games.
I just want to pass.
I know I'm alive.
See I've been trying to fucking leave again.
I'm attached to the pen set the sky so I'm fine.
I just got a spell there.
Don't watch me, Bob.
What I saw right now is a lack of words.
Just got a spell there and you'll be fine.